Curriculum Vitae

Li, Kwing Hei

November, 2022

Basic Info

Preferred name: Hei Li Email: Hei.Li@cl.cam.ac.uk Web: https://hei411.github.io/

Research Topics

The very heart of my research interests is programming languages. I develop mathematical models and methods that enable us to design, implement, and reason about computer programs.

At the moment, I am also interested in other related topics, such as formal verification, and the theory of concurrency and distributed systems.

Education

2022 - Now	M.Phil in Advanced Computer Science
	King's College, University of Cambridge
2019 - 2022	B.A. Hons. in Computer Science with Mathematics (1st class)
	Churchill College, University of Cambridge
	Title: Type Systems for Functional Reactive Programming [pdf]

Experience

2022	Research Intern
	Max Planck Institute for Software Systems
	Supervisor: Prof. Derek Dreyer and Mr. Michael Sammler
2021	Undergraduate Research Intern
	University of Cambridge Machine Learning Systems Lab
	Supervisor: Prof. Nicholas Lane and Dr. Pedro Porto Buarque de Gusmao
2020	Automation Engineer Intern
	DreamsAI, Hong Kong

Roles

2022 - Now	Safety and Welfare Officer
	Churchill College Boat Club
2021 - 2022	Computing Officer
	Churchill College JCR Committee
2020 - 2022	Coxing Captain
	Churchill College Boat Club

Awards

2022	Beatrice Blore-Browne Prize Scholarship
2022	Cambridge Trust and King's College TPP Alan Turing Scholarship
2022	University of Oxford Hong Kong Jockey Club Graduate Scholarship (declined)
2022	Churchill Prize Scholarship
2021	Beatrice Blore-Browne Prize Scholarship
2021	Churchill Prize Scholarship
2021	Churchill Computer Science Talks Series – Audience Favourite Talk
2020	Churchill Honorary Scholarship

Publications

2022 Secure Aggregation for Federated Learning in Flower [pdf]

Kwing Hei Li, Pedro Porto Buarque de Gusmão, Daniel J. Beutel, Nicholas D. Lane In DistributedML 2021: Proceedings of the 2nd ACM International Workshop on Distributed Machine Learning

Unpublished Drafts

2022 Formalizing May's Theorem [pdf]

Kwing Hei Li